

Web | App developer 29 boulevard Amiral Courbet Oullins, Oklahoma, 69600 pashaborges@gmail.com I'm a web developer with 5 years of experience designing websites and standalone applications.

I have worked with clients in a variety of industries, including healthcare, finance, and e-commerce, and have designed everything from small business websites to large enterprise applications.

I pride myself on my ability to communicate effectively with clients and deliver projects on time and on budget.

I understand the importance of clear communication and am always available to answer questions and provide updates on project progress.

I'm available online from 2 am GMT to 5 pm GMT, and I offer 7 days of free support related to my work, as well as a service guarantee on all of my projects.

#### **KEY SKILLS**

- · Javascript, PHP, Java/Spring
- · React.js, Redux, Next.js, Angular, Vue.js
- · Laravel, Express.js, Node.js, Python, Django
- MySQL, MongoDB, SQLite, PostgreSQL
- · Solidity, Web3, Etherum, Blockchain
- CSS3, HTML5, Jquery/Prototype, Bootstrap
- C/C++, C# Application Development, .NET framework
- · Rest API, GraphQL, ElasticSearch
- · AWS S3/EC2, Docker/kubernetes, Heroku, Azure
- · Android, iOS, Swift, Flutter, React Native, Cordova

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

June 2022 -January 2023 FRONTEND

DEVELOPER

https://www.wcirb.com/

The WCIRB is California's trusted, objective provider of actuarially-based information and research, advisory pure premium rates and educational services integral to a healthy workers' compensation system.

Enhance member insurer success by providing analytics and tools through active collaboration to facilitate decision making, identify emerging trends and understand system implications.

- Built a partner-widget to help insurance providers integrate.
- Implemented B2B, B2C system for individual customers and businesses to make transactions.
- SPA development and advanced javascript functional programming.
- Onboarding website for customers to make transactions secure and safe.
- · Logging and log analytics using ElasticSearch
- Implemented Verification system for KYC and KYB. (Integrated Veriff SDK)
- Worked with microservices for payments and third party integrations

June 2021 -May 2022 **MOBILE** 

Auto parts separate platform

**WCIRB** 

DEVELOPER

https://web.autom.com.my/admin

https://web.autom.com.my/retailer

https://web.autom.com.my/wholesaler

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.autom.app.automapp

https://apps.apple.com/us/app/autommalaysia/id1619973924

The Autom is Malaysia's trusted, which is based on B2B and B2C system for multi-vendor marketplace.

It's for car separate parts, order and delivery system.

There are multi roles such as admin, wholesaler, retailer, customer

- Built Mobile versions using flutter
- Laravel and Mysql Backend
- Admin panel
- Web version for retailer and wholesaler
- Firebase integration for live chat

# January 2019 - June 2021

# FULL STACK

ClickClaims Claims Management Solutions

# DEVELOPER

https://www.clickclaims.com/ https://www.forestadmin.com/

ClickClaims is a Software as a Service (SaaS) claims management solution for Property and Casualty Insurance Carriers, Independent Claim Adjusters, Third Party Administrators, and Specialty Claim Service Providers.

- Build several web applications using MERN, MEAN stack.
- · Used Angular JS model + Java/Spring.
- Talent design and cost effective plans, eyecatching designs, mobile responsive pages.
- Built an admin dashboard using ForestAdmin Integrated third party services to Django backend.

July 2017 -December 2018

## FULL STACK

HereIam, Virginia

## **DEVELOPER**

https://hereiamfront.azurewebsites.net/

https://hereiam.church/

Here I Am is a new engagement app created to help church congregations stay connected during worship events and throughout the week.

- Used SQL server, .NET framework for backend to manage posts and events.
- Mobile app users get notified when an upcoming worship begins.
- Church administrators make posts and schedule worship events on the website.
- Search Engine Optimization and Azure DevOps.
- Testing new browser features and decide if results are useful and satisfying to meet user needs.
- Good experience with Spring(MVC), Springboot, Maven, Hibernate.
- Used React and Angular for fronten.

## **EDUCATION**

2017 -August 2018 IT ARCHITECTURE DESIGNER School for Computing and Advanced Techniques, France

September 2019 -October 2020 IT ARCHITECTURE DESIGNER University of the Mediterranean (Aix-Marseille II), France